<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index on Den of devils</title>
    <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index on Den of devils</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yourdevilfriends.art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: Tips regarding Web accessibility</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/blog/posts/accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/blog/posts/accessibility/</guid>
      <description>Tutorial: Tips regarding Web accessibility Whenever I browse personal websites, it&amp;rsquo;s often I notice a lack of thought from their Webmasters when it comes to browsing the Web in a way different than their own.
Back when I hosted my sites on Neocities, I ended up learning a lot about Web accessibility and why it matters. I very firmly believe that the indie Web shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be gatekept from people who genuinely want to learn more about it, especially if it&amp;rsquo;s over something they can&amp;rsquo;t control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bigger smile</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/biggersmile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/biggersmile/</guid>
      <description>Bigger smile Originally the original piece was going to feature Alastor upside down, but I decided against it.
Made with Procreate.
Alternate versions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malware</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/malware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/malware/</guid>
      <description>Malware Angel Dust was inspired by PostPet, while Alastor was inspired by the infamous BonziBuddy.
Made with Procreate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World / The star</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/theworld_thestar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/theworld_thestar/</guid>
      <description>The World Meet Drazkise, a character for a D&amp;amp;D campaign based on magical girls and Super Sentai. His «superhero» outfit is inspired by the World tarot card.
Made with Procreate.
The Star This one is Memoru, my backup for the same campaign that doubles as Drazkise&amp;rsquo;s roommate. His magical boy outfit is inspired by the Star tarot card.
Much like the previous piece, this was made with Procreate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 1st</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/april1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/gallery/posts/april1st/</guid>
      <description>April 1st Something quick based on this official Hazbin Hotel art.
Made with Krita, using Pixel Glade&amp;rsquo;s dithering brushes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/about/</guid>
      <description>About The website Powered by Hugo Hosted with GitHub Pages Tested on Firefox Is mobile-friendly, maybe. Made with blood, sweat, tears, and even some amount of effort The guy himself I&amp;rsquo;m Bruno «devils» A., a 25 year-old artist from Portugal. He/him or they/them if you absolutely must refer to me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been diagnosed with schizophrenia, so that might come up in my art or blog. I&amp;rsquo;m usually pretty coherent though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fursonas</title>
      <link>https://yourdevilfriends.art/fursonas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yourdevilfriends.art/fursonas/</guid>
      <description>Fursonas &amp;hellip; Yeah.
Sugar Bizuto Kuyata Creep Winters Sugar Art by Patrick
Vital statistics: Full name: Sugar Brown Species: Tapeworm Gender: Boy-adjacent thing Bizuto Vital statistics: Full name: Bizuto «Bizu» Artesia Species: Cat / Angel cat / Demon cat Gender: Masc-aligned agender Kuyata Art by Patrick
Vital statistics: Full name: Kuyata Species: Cosmic bull Gender: Male Creep Art by Terry
Vital statistics: Full name: Creepazoid Species: Dog Gender: Male Winters Vital statistics: Full name: Winters Gone Species: Bicorn Gender: Agender </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
